<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yoga Demo app</string>


    <string name="back1">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Lat Pulldown Machine, Lat Bar</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Sitting, thighs under the padded parts, the bar grasped in pronation, hands more apart than shoulder width. Keep elbows pointed outwards and back straight. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Pull the bar at the back of the neck. Keep the contraction for a moment before slowly returning to the initial position. During the movement, do not let your elbows come forward. </p></string>
    <string name="back2">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbell, Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Hind Deltoids, biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Place your left knee and left hand on the bench with your chest parallel to the floor. Keep your right foot on the ground and grasp the dumbbell still on the ground in your right hand in a neutral grip. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Keeping your arm close to your body, lift the dumbbell as high as possible by raising your elbow and keeping your forearm perpendicular to the ground. Once your series is over, do the same with the other arm. </p></string>
    <string name="back3">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -seated rowing machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Hind Deltoids, biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Sitting on the machine's bench with your feet on the wedge. Grasp the double handle attached to the cable with both hands. Keep back straight and knees slightly bent. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Pull the load towards your abdomen. Tighten your back at the end of the movement by bringing your elbows as far back as possible. Then slowly return to the initial position. </p></string>
    <string name="back4">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -T-Bar machine, plates</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Rear deltoids, biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Use a T-Bar machine (or place a barbell in the corner of a room). Stand with feet either side of the bar, bend your knees, and bow forward so that your chest is directly over the plate on the barbell. Grab the handle in both hands. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Keeping your posture still, pull the handles so that the plate rises towards your chest. Pause just before it touches, and then slowly lower it back down. </p></string>
    <string name="back5">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Pull bar</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Grasp the pull bar using a pronated grip, head slightly up, hands wider than shoulders width apart, and elbows slightly bent. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Do a pull up by pulling your chin towards the bar. Then come back slowly to the starting position. Your segments’ length, your strength, and your shoulders’ mobility will determine how high you can pull yourself up. </p></string>


    <string name="leg1">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbells, stepper</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Buttocks and thigh muscles\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Standing with legs hip-width apart, one dumbbell in each hand. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Keeping the bust straight, take a step forward and slowly descend until the forward thigh is parallel to the ground. Then return to the original position. Once you have completed your series, do the same with the other leg. </p></string>
    <string name="leg2">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Barbell</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Thigh and buttock muscles \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Standing with the bar resting on your upper chest and deltoids. Grasp the bar with your hands for a good support. Keep your head straight \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Bend your knees and hips as if you were sitting down. While keeping your back straight, let your buttocks go backwards, which will tilt your chest slightly forwards to make the movement as natural as possible. The moment your thighs are parallel to the ground, move upwards, doing the movement in the opposite direction. Given the complexity of this movement, ask a trainer in your gym to show you how to perform it correctly the first time.  </p></string>
    <string name="leg3">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Mat</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Core Muscles \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Glute Muscles\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Get down onto the mat. Position yourself on your hands and knees. Place your hands directly under your shoulders and your knees right under your hips. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-While maintaining a neutral spine and bracing your core, extend one arm straight out in front of you and extend the opposite leg backwards until they’re parallel with the ground and you’ve created a straight line with your body. Keep your hips parallel to the ground. Hold this position briefly and then lower back to the starting position. Repeat with the opposite side.  </p></string>
    <string name="leg4">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Lever Stepper Machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Buttocks and thigh muscles \n\n</p>
        <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Glute Muscles \n\n</p></string>
    <string name="leg5">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Seated Calf Raise Machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Calves\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Sitting on the machine with the front of the feet on the wedge and the lower thighs under the padded parts \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- While contracting the calves, raise your heels as high as possible. Stay in the high position for a moment, feeling the contraction well. Then slowly lower your heels by stretching your calves. </p></string>
    <string name="chest1">   <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbells, Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Chest\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Front deltoids, triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Lying on the bench, your feet flat on the floor, one dumbbell in each hand, pronation grip. Hold the dumbbells at your sides at chest height. Your forearms should be perpendicular to the ground. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-By contracting your pectorals, push the load against upwards until your arms are almost extended, then return to the initial position.

During the entire movement:

Keep your elbows on the outside to put maximum stress on your pectorals and minimum stress on your anterior deltoids and triceps.
Keep your shoulders flat against the bench.  </p></string>
    <string name="chest2">   <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbells, Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- chest\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Front deltoids\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Lying on the bench, your feet flat on the floor, one dumbbell in each hand. Hold the weights in a neutral grip, arms outstretched above your chest.  \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Slowly lower the dumbbells to the sides in an arc with your arms until you feel a stretch in your pectorals. Do not go below shoulder level. Then return to the original position, performing the same arc.

During the whole movement:

Keep your elbows pointed outward and slightly bent to reduce stress on the joint.
Keep your shoulders flat against the bench. </p></string>
    <string name="chest3">   <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Curlbell, Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-chest \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Front deltoids, triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Lying on the bench, your feet flat on the floor. Grasp the bar with a grip narrow than shoulder width. Your forearms should be perpendicular to the floor. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Unhook the bar and slowly lower it to the lower part of your chest. As you contract your pectorals, push the load upwards until your arms are almost straight.

During the whole movement:

Keep your elbows on the outside to put maximum stress on your chest and minimum stress on your anterior deltoids and triceps.
Keep your shoulders flat against the bench. </p></string>
    <string name="chest4">   <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-chest \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Deltoids, Triceps, Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-  Face down, one arm outstretched,  resting on the floor and aligned with your pectoral muscles. Legs stretched and face pointed towards the ground\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Slowly bend your arm, letting your chest come closer to the ground, until your elbows form a 90 degrees angle. Then return to the starting position by pushing on your hand and then repeat the same with other hand. </p></string>
    <string name="tricep1">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Cable Machine, Pressdown Bar</p>
        <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Standing facing the pulley, grasping the bar with a pronation grip, hands shoulder width apart. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Carry out an extension of the forearms until your arms are fully extended. In this position, contract your triceps for a moment and then slowly return to the initial position. Keep your elbows close to your body during the whole movement. </p></string>
    <string name="tricep2">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Tricep\n\n</p>
        <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Chest\n\n</p></string>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Feet are placed on a raised surface with your hands on a lower surface or the ground.\n\n</p>
    <string name="tricep3">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbell</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Place your left knee and left hand on a bench, with your chest parallel to the floor. Keep your right foot on the ground and grasp the dumbbell in your right hand. Keeping it close to your body, raise the top of your right arm until it is parallel to the ground. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Perform an extension of the right arm. When it is fully extended, contract your triceps for a moment before returning to the initial position. Once you have completed your series, do the same with the other arm. </p></string>
    <string name="tricep4">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Triceps, front deltoids\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Set up for the bench dip by placing two flat benches parallel to one another to around your legs’ length. Keeping your back straight and your arms outstretched, place your hands on the edge of one bench at about shoulder’s width and put your heels on the edge of the other bench, legs and buttocks swinging in the air (see picture). \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- While keeping your elbows tucked in, slowly flex them until they are at a 90° angle. Then slowly come back to the starting position and squeeze your triceps at the top. Keep your back straight throughout the movement. Repeat for desired reps. </p></string>
    <string name="biceps1">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-  </p></string>
    <string name="biceps2">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -EZ Barbell,Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Standing with knees slightly bent and back straight. Hold the EZ bar with your hands in supination\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Without making a movement of bust, raise the EZ bar by bending the forearms. Contract your biceps in high position, then let the bar slowly come down again in the initial position. Keep your elbows close to your body during the movement. </p></string>
    <string name="biceps3">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-  </p></string>
    <string name="biceps4">  <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbell, bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Sitting on a bench, hold a dumbbell in your right hand, supine grip. With your chest slightly bent forward, rest your elbow on the inside of your right thigh, leaving your arm relaxed towards the ground \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Slowly bend your forearm as you bring the dumbbell towards your right shoulder. Contract your biceps in the high position, then slowly return to the initial position. Once your series is completed, move to the other arm. </p></string>
    <string name="shoulder1">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbells, bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Deltoids\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Sitting on a bench with your back well supported against the backrest. Hold the dumbbells in your hands (pronation grip) a little above shoulder height. Your elbows are on the outside and your forearms are perpendicular to the ground. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Push the dumbbells upwards. Until your arms are fully extended. Then return to the original position </p></string>
    <string name="shoulder2">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Smith machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Deltoids\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:-Sitting on a bench with your back well supported against the backrest. Position the bench so that the bar drops just in front of your face. Grasp the bar with your hands in pronation. Your back is well supported against the backrest, your elbows are on the outside and your forearms are perpendicular to the ground. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Unhook the bar and slowly bring it to the height of your chin. Contract your shoulders by pushing the load upwards. Stop the movement just before your arms are fully extended. Then return to the down position. </p></string>
    <string name="shoulder3">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Barbell</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Shoulders\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Stand upright with a barbell resting on your upper chest and shoulders and elbows pointed out in front of you. Feet should be shoulder width apart.\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Bend knees slightly and then drive upwards, pushing the barbell straight up in the air and finishing with arms extended above your head. Pause, and then return to starting position. </p></string>
    <string name="shoulder4">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbells</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Shoulders\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Triceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Stand upright with a dumbbell resting on each shoulder and elbows pointed out in front of you. Feet should be shoulder width apart.\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Bend knees slightly and then drive upwards, pushing the dumbbells straight up in the air and finishing with arms extended above your head. Pause, and then return to starting position. </p></string>
    <string name="shoulder5">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -EZ Barbell</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Deltoids, trapezius muscles\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Biceps and forearms\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Standing, holding the bar in front of you, pronation grip, hands shoulder-width apart.\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Lift the bar vertically to chest height. Contract for a moment, then return to the starting position. During the whole movement, keep the bar close to the body and the elbows higher than the wrists. </p></string>
    <string name="shoulder6">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- \n\n</p>
        <p><b>Execution</b>:-  </p></string>


</resources>