<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yoga Demo app</string>


    <string name="back1">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Lat Pulldown Machine, Lat Bar</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Sitting, thighs under the padded parts, the bar grasped in pronation, hands more apart than shoulder width. Keep elbows pointed outwards and back straight. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Pull the bar at the back of the neck. Keep the contraction for a moment before slowly returning to the initial position. During the movement, do not let your elbows come forward. </p></string>
    <string name="back2">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbell, Bench</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Hind Deltoids, biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Place your left knee and left hand on the bench with your chest parallel to the floor. Keep your right foot on the ground and grasp the dumbbell still on the ground in your right hand in a neutral grip. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Keeping your arm close to your body, lift the dumbbell as high as possible by raising your elbow and keeping your forearm perpendicular to the ground. Once your series is over, do the same with the other arm. </p></string>
    <string name="back3">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Rowing Machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Hind deltoids, biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Sitting on the machine's bench with your feet on the wedge. Grasp the double handle attached to the cable with both hands. Keep back straight and knees slightly bent. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Pull the load towards your abdomen. Tighten your back at the end of the movement by bringing your elbows as far back as possible. Then slowly return to the initial position. </p></string>
    <string name="back4">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -T-Bar machine, plates</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Rear deltoids, biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Use a T-Bar machine (or place a barbell in the corner of a room). Stand with feet either side of the bar, bend your knees, and bow forward so that your chest is directly over the plate on the barbell. Grab the handle in both hands. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Keeping your posture still, pull the handles so that the plate rises towards your chest. Pause just before it touches, and then slowly lower it back down. </p></string>
    <string name="back5">    <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Pull bar</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Back\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:- Biceps\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Grasp the pull bar using a pronated grip, head slightly up, hands wider than shoulders width apart, and elbows slightly bent. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Do a pull up by pulling your chin towards the bar. Then come back slowly to the starting position. Your segments’ length, your strength, and your shoulders’ mobility will determine how high you can pull yourself up. </p></string>


    <string name="leg1">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Dumbbells, stepper</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Buttocks and thigh muscles\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Standing with legs hip-width apart, one dumbbell in each hand. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- Keeping the bust straight, take a step forward and slowly descend until the forward thigh is parallel to the ground. Then return to the original position. Once you have completed your series, do the same with the other leg. </p></string>
    <string name="leg2">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Barbell</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Thigh and buttock muscles \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Standing with the bar resting on your upper chest and deltoids. Grasp the bar with your hands for a good support. Keep your head straight \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-Bend your knees and hips as if you were sitting down. While keeping your back straight, let your buttocks go backwards, which will tilt your chest slightly forwards to make the movement as natural as possible. The moment your thighs are parallel to the ground, move upwards, doing the movement in the opposite direction. Given the complexity of this movement, ask a trainer in your gym to show you how to perform it correctly the first time.  </p></string>
    <string name="leg3">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Mat</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Core Muscles \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Glute Muscles\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Get down onto the mat. Position yourself on your hands and knees. Place your hands directly under your shoulders and your knees right under your hips. \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:-While maintaining a neutral spine and bracing your core, extend one arm straight out in front of you and extend the opposite leg backwards until they’re parallel with the ground and you’ve created a straight line with your body. Keep your hips parallel to the ground. Hold this position briefly and then lower back to the starting position. Repeat with the opposite side.  </p></string>
    <string name="leg4">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Lever Stepper Machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:-Buttocks and thigh muscles \n\n</p>
        <p><b>Secondary muscles</b>:-Glute Muscles \n\n</p></string>
    <string name="leg5">     <p><b>Equipment required</b> -Seated Calf Raise Machine</p>
                             <p><b>Main muscles</b>:- Calves\n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Starting position</b>:- Sitting on the machine with the front of the feet on the wedge and the lower thighs under the padded parts \n\n</p>
                             <p><b>Execution</b>:- While contracting the calves, raise your heels as high as possible. Stay in the high position for a moment, feeling the contraction well. Then slowly lower your heels by stretching your calves. </p></string>
    <string name="pose11">    Step 1:- Lie on the floor with elbows directly beneath your shoulders and legs fully extended.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Raise your torso into the air until it makes a straight line from your shoulders to your ankles. Tighten your stomach, squeeze your butt.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose12">    Step 1:- Lie down on the floor placing your feet either under something that will not move or by having a partner hold them. Your legs should be bent at the knees. Elevate your upper body so that it creates an imaginary V-shape with your thighs. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Your arms should be fully extended in front of you perpendicular to your torso and with the hands clasped. This is the starting position.\n\n
                             Step 3:- This is the starting position. Twist your torso to the right side until your arms are parallel with the floor while breathing out. \n\n
                             Step 4:- Hold the contraction for a second and move back to the starting position while breathing out. Now move to the opposite side performing the same techniques you applied to the right side. Repeat for the recommended amount of repetitions.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose13">    Step 1:- Lie on your back with your knees bent, feet flat and hip width. \n\n
                             Step 2:- Lower your pelvis 2 inches from the floor. Squeeze your glutes and lift your pelvis back to bridge position.

                            </string>
    <string name="pose14">    Step 1:- Lie facedown on the floor with your arms extended in front of you and your leg extended behind you. \n\n
                             Step 2:- In one movement,engage your glutes and lower back to raise your arms,legs,and chest off the floor.\n\n
                             Step 3:- Hold for a count,then slowly return to the starting position.
                            </string>
    <string name="pose15">   Step 1:- Stand, extend arms 90° to sides, bend forward 90° at waist.\n\n
                             Step 2:- Looking at the floor, rotate torso to touch hand to foot, rotate for other hand. \n\n
                             Step 3:- Head will follow chest action. </string>

</resources>